export const quizzes = [
    {
        question: "How much (in percent) is the PST and GST combined? (Note: this is also called HST (harmonized sale tax)",
        options: ["11%", "12%", "13%", "14%"],
        correctOption: "12%",
        rightPoints: 3,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    {
        question: "What is an example of a  “need”?",
        link: "https://blog.cypruscu.com/teen-financial-toolkit-wants-vs.-needs",
        options: ["Toys", "Water", "Laptop", "Candy"],
        correctOption: "Water",
        rightPoints: 2,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    {
        question: "What is a “need”?",
        link: "https://blog.cypruscu.com/teen-financial-toolkit-wants-vs.-needs",
        options: ["A gift ", "Something that you have to have to survive or complete a task", "An item or thing you want to upgrade", "The newest products on the shelf"],
        correctOption: "Something that you have to have to survive or complete a task", "An item or thing you want to upgrade", "The newest products on the shelf",
        rightPoints: 1,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    {
        question: "What is an example of a “want”?",
        link: "https://blog.cypruscu.com/teen-financial-toolkit-wants-vs.-needs",
        options: ["Food", "Shelter", "Water", "Pop"],
        correctOption: "Pop",
        rightPoints: 2,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    {
        question: "What is a budget?",
        link: "https://www.mathsisfun.com/money/budget.html",
        options: ["A plan to maximize profit", "The minimum amount of money you will spend", "The maximum money you will earn in a week", "A plan for income and spendings over time"],
        correctOption: "A plan for income and spendings over time",
        rightPoints: 1,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    {
        question: "What is profit?",
        link: "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ksnKQpdMgL0",
        options: ["The total amount of money you make in a day", "The amount of money made after subtracting fixed and variables costs", "The amount of money that is deducted from your earnings", "The rate of earnings growth"],
        correctOption: "The amount of money made after subtracting fixed and variables costs",
        rightPoints: 1,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    {
        question: "What is revenue?",
        link: "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ksnKQpdMgL0",
        options: ["Spendings", "The rate of earnings growth", "Income", "The amount of money deducted from your earnings"],
        correctOption: "Income",
        rightPoints: 1,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not exempt from PST?",
        link: "https://www2.gov.bc.ca/gov/content/taxes/sales-taxes/pst/exemptions",
        options: ["School supplies", "Unprocessed foods", "Toys", "Safety Equipment"],
        correctOption: "Toys",
        rightPoints: 3,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },
    
    {
        question: "What is a fixed expense?",
        link: "https://www2.gov.bc.ca/gov/content/taxes/sales-taxes/pst/exemptions",
        options: ["An expense that stays the same every month", "An expense for fixing your house", "The cost of fixing broken equipment", "The cost of fixing broken electronics"],
        correctOption: "An expense that stays the same every month",
        rightPoints: 2,
        wrongPoints: -1
    },

    {
        question: "What is a variable expense?",
        link: "https://www2.gov.bc.ca/gov/content/taxes/sales-taxes/pst/exemptions",
        options: ["The rate of change of an expense", "The name for the math done to calculate expenses", "An expense that changes over time", "The range that an expense can be"],
        correctOption: "An expense that changes over time",
        rightPoints: 2,
        wrongPoints: -1
    }
];